# **Bowen Yu**

## **Computer Science**

I am a new graduate computer science student from Oregon State University, seeking for a software engineer position. Have 7 years coding experiences, including 6 months industry working experience. Have good skills in multiple languages, especially Java and JavaScript, and Object-Oriented conception.



# **Experience**

### 2017-11 -2017-12

### A restaurant web application

- Developed the restaurant web application in HTML, CSS and JavaScript, and Implemented the responsive web app in bootstrap framework to adapt its layout to the viewing environment.
- Developed that dynamically inserting the main content of the home page by using Ajax to make the page loading faster when just only a small amount of updating in the page.
- Used a Heroku app to service JSON with the data that is needed for the different menu categories, so that it could dynamically insert the menu categories when the user clicks on the menu tile.

### 2017-04 -2017-06

### **Dribbbo -- An App of Android Mobile**

- Developed Dribbbo in Java and Android Studio. Users can access to their profile, likes, and bucket collections.
- Designed the App that can allow users to upload photos or video to their account and also can do search, delete, and modify about their uploaded images.
- Using the RecyclerView to implement the user interface in order to make the UI more flexible. Also use the same technique to implement infinite loading list.

#### 2017-03 -2017-03

#### A Battle Flight Game

- Developed a web game following MVC pattern and using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Generate 3 flights with "head", "wings" and "body" automatically and randomly.
- Implemented to allow user to input a correct pattern coordinate number of the grid to the guess if the ship is hit or missed.

### 2016-01 -

#### OpenGL project

#### 2016-03

- Using openGL to develop 3D objects and modify the surface of the objects.
- Modify the surface texture of the object by changing the parameter of the light.
- Using cube-mapping to implement 3D environment.

#### 2011-09 -

### Internship

2012-06

Neusoft Corporation, Shenyang, China

· Mainly trained to participate in developing coding skill.



# **Education**

### 2016-01 - Oregon State University

2017-04

• Degree: Master. Major: Computer Science. GPA: 3.55

### 2008-09 - Harbin University of Science and Technology, China

2012-06

• Degree: Bachelor. Major: Software Engineering. GPA: 3.7



# **Personal Info**

#### E-mail

yubowen89@gmail.com

#### **Phone**

541-745-8631

#### Address

1220 N Fair Oaks Ave, Sunnyvale, CA



### **Skills**

Programming languages: Java,

Python, C

Web Design: HTML, CSS,

**JavaScript** 

Database: Microsoft SQL Server,

Mysql

Frameworks: jQuery, Bootstrap

Operating System: Mac OS, Linux,

windows

Version Control System(VCS): Git